const data = [
    {
      question: " He's still sleeping, ________",
      answer_1: "do he?",
      answer_2: "isn't he?",
      answer_3: "wasn't he?",
      answer_4: "aren't he?",
      correct: "isn't he?",
    },
    {
      question:
        " Yesterday, we ______ a very interesting conference call about the new ERP project. ",
      answer_1: "are having",
      answer_2: "have",
      answer_3: "had",
      answer_4: "were had",
      correct: "had",
    },
    {
      question: " The plane _____ at New York's Kennedy Airport. ",
      answer_1: "Took off",
      answer_2: "Took down",
      answer_3: "landed",
      answer_4: "Drove",
      correct: "landed",
    },
    {
      question:
        " Compound Nouns: Thomas White, who orchestrated ___________ rescue packages, will address the group",
      answer_1: "Multi billion-dollars",
      answer_2: "Multi billions dollars",
      answer_3: "Multi billion dollar",
      answer_4: "Multi billion-dollar",
      correct: "Multi billion-dollar",
    },
    {
      question:
        " Prepositions: She always gets up early ______ the morning, so she can make it to class ______ time.",
      answer_1: "In ---- on",
      answer_2: "On ---- on",
      answer_3: "In ---- in",
      answer_4: "By ---- in",
      correct: "In ---- on",
    },
    {
      question: " dentify the next number in the series:1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, _____",
      answer_1: "20",
      answer_2: "13",
      answer_3: "9",
      answer_4: "10",
      correct: "13",
    },
    {
      question: "   A pad costs 33 cents. How much will 5 pads cost?",
      answer_1: "$2.28",
      answer_2: "$1.45",
      answer_3: "$1.10",
      answer_4: "$5.5",
      correct: "$2.28",
    },
    {
      question: "  What is the square root of 8?",
      answer_1: "16",
      answer_2: "4.466",
      answer_3: "3.56",
      answer_4: "2.82",
      correct: "2:82",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Identify the missing number in the series.0.18, 0.36, 0.72, _____, 2.88",
      answer_1: "1.62",
      answer_2: "0.9",
      answer_3: "1.44",
      answer_4: "1.26",
      correct: "1.44",
    },
    {
      question:
        " Kevin is 21 years old and his sister is a third his age. When Kevin is 36, what will be the age of his sister?",
      answer_1: "36",
      answer_2: "24",
      answer_3: "28",
      answer_4: "22",
      correct: "22",
    },
    {
      question: "Which HTML element defines the title of a document?",
      answer_1: "title",
      answer_2: "head",
      answer_3: "meta",
      answer_4: "html",
      correct: "title",
    },
  
    {
      question:
        "_______ attribute is used to specify where to open the linked document.",
      answer_1: "target",
      answer_2: "coords",
      answer_3: "rel",
      answer_4: "None of the above",
      correct: "target",
    },
    {
      question: " The HTML tags are all",
      answer_1: "In lower case",
      answer_2: "In upper case",
      answer_3: "Case sensitive",
      answer_4: "Not case sensitive",
      correct: "Not case sensitive",
    },
    {
      question:
        "A _____ tag is used to specify that the browser is to fetch and use an external style sheet file",
      answer_1: "src",
      answer_2: "sheet",
      answer_3: "link",
      answer_4: "None of the above",
      correct: "link",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following property is used to set the background image of an element ?",
      answer_1: "background-repeat",
      answer_2: "background-position",
      answer_3: "background-image",
      answer_4: "background-color",
      correct: "background-image",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following property is used to increase or decrease the size of a font ?",
      answer_1: "font-weight",
      answer_2: "font",
      answer_3: "font-size",
      answer_4: "None of the above",
      correct: "font-size",
    },
    {
      question: " Local Browser used for validations on the Web Pages uses",
      answer_1: "js",
      answer_2: "java",
      answer_3: "HTML",
      answer_4: "CSS",
      correct: "js",
    },
    {
      question: "JavaScript code can be called by using",
      answer_1: "RMI",
      answer_2: "Preprocessor",
      answer_3: "Function / Method",
      answer_4: "None of the above",
      correct: "Function / Method",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following Attribute is used to include External JS code inside your HTML Document ?",
      answer_1: "link",
      answer_2: "script",
      answer_3: "ext",
      answer_4: "src",
      correct: "src",
    },
    {
      question: "Which was the first browser to support JavaScript ?",
      answer_1: "Google Chrome",
      answer_2: "Netscape",
      answer_3: "Mozilla Firefox",
      answer_4: "IE",
      correct: "Netscape",
    },
  ];